A Guide to the Papers of K. Edward Lay
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Architecture Correspondence
  - Architecture Correspondence 1991 (Box 54)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1992 (Box 54)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1993 (Box 54)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1994 (Box 54)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1995 (Box 55)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1996 (Box 55)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1997 (Box 55)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1998 (Box 55)
  - Architecture Correspondence 1999 (Box 55)
  - Architecture Correspondence 2000 (Box 55)
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County Houses-A n.d. (Box 56)
    [Ackley; Albemarle Farm; Alberene; Alden House; Alderman House; Allendale; Allwood House; American Four Square; Anchorage; Arrowhead; Ash Lawn; Auburn Hill]
  - Albemarle County Houses n.d. (Box 56)
    [miscellaneous and identified]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ba-Be n.d. (Box 56)
    [Bachelor's Quarters; Bailey House; Balcard-Powell House; Ballard-Abel House; Bancroft; Barclay House; Barksdale Day House; Barracks; Barringer Mansion; Batesville houses; Batna; Beauerdam Farm; Bellair; Bellair, Wingfield; Bel Aire; Belle Grove (Valmont); Belle Haven; Belmont, Charlottesville; Belmont, Brown's Cove; Belvoir; Belvoir 2; Belvoir 3; Bemiss House; Ben Coolyn House; Bentivar]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Bi-Bo n.d. (Box 56)
    [Bird Haven, Greenwood; Birdwood; Bishop House; Black Family and house; Blair House, Scottsville; Bleak House (Holly House); Blenheim; Bloomfield; Blueridge Farm; Bonahora; Boxwood]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Br-Bu n.d. (Box 56)
    [Branch Point; Brand Hartman ouse; Breezy Oaks; Briar Creek Farm; Bridle Spur; Brightberry; Brockenbrough; Brook Hill (Minor); Brookhill (Dunkum); Brooks Farm; Albert Brooks House; Brown-Parrott House; Brownsville House; Buck Island; Buena Vista; Butler-Norris House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Castle Hill n.d. (Box 56)
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ca-Ch n.d. (Box 56)
    [Canaan; Carr House, The Meadows; Carr's Hill Carriage House; Carr House, Charlottesville; Hugh Carr House; Carrollton Manor; Carrs Brook; Carrs Grove; Carr's Hill Dorm; Carter-Gilmer House; Carver House; Castalia; Castlebrook; Catterton Place; Cedar Grove; Cedars; Cherry Hill; Cherry Valley; Chester, Scottsville; Chestnut Avenue smokehouse/plantation office; Chiswell; Christmas Hill; Church Hill]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Charlottesville houses n.d. (Box 56)
    [miscellaneous and unidentified]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ci-Cr n.d. (Box 56)
    [Cismont Manor; Clermont; Cliffside, Scottsville; Clover Fields; Clifton; Clover Hill; Cobham Park; Cole House (Bollingwood); Colle House; Colonial House, Scottsville; Comer House; Conduff House; Carolyn Cox Log House; Crestwood; Crutchfield]
  - Albemarle County Houses-D n.d. (Box 56)
    [Darby's Folly; Davis House; Dabney (Dinsmore) House; Doll House; Donegal; Dovedale; Duke House; R. T. W. Duke House; Dulaney House; Dunkum-Dice House; Dunkum-Spooner House; Dumlora 3; Dunn House; Dyer House]
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ea-Ed n.d. (Box 57)
    [East Belmont; Edgehill; Edgemont; Ednam; Edgemont, Stony Point Road; Edgewood; Edgeworth; Edwards House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-El-Ev n.d. (Box 57)
    [Ellerslie; Enderly; Enniscorthy; Ernscliff Log House; Esmont House; Estes Farm; Estouteville; Everett House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-F n.d. (Box 57)
    [Fairmont; Fairview; The Farm; Farmington; Faulkner House; Feathers; Fielding; Fifth Street House; Finally; Findowrie; Forest Hill; Forest Lodge; Foster House; Fosteria; Four Acres; Fowler House; Franklin; Fray House; Fuller-Bailey House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-G n.d. (Box 57)
    [Gale Hill; Gallison Hall; Giddings; Gilmer-Wood House (Drurywood House; Glen Esk; Glendower; Glen Echo; Glenmore; Glentivar; Gooch House; Goodwin Farm; Grassmere; Milton Grigg House; The Grove (Barksdale-Totty House; Guthrie Hall]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ha-He n.d. (Box 57)
    [Haden House; Halifax House; Hampstead; Hard Bargain; J. W. Hatch House; Hatton Grange; Hawkins-Holmes House; Hawkins-Wondree House; Head of Creek Plantation; Headquarters; Heiskell House; Heiskeg House (Livers House); Herndon House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Hi-Hu n.d. (Box 57)
    [High Meadows; High Mowing; The Hill, Altamont Circle; Hillel; Hilltop; Hodges-Gleason House; Holly Fork; Hollymead; Holmes House; Home Place; Homestead House; Home Tract; Hopewell; Horseshoe; Horseshoe Retreat; Hotopp House; Houchins House; Hough House; Lindsay House; Lucy Howard House; Hudson-Smith House; Hugh House; Dr. Humphries House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-I n.d. (Box 57)
    [Idylwood; International House; Ivy Creek Farm]
  - Albemarle County Houses-J n.d. (Box 57)
    [Nanny Cox Jackson House; Jarman (Brugger) House; Jarman-Cree House; Jarman-Walker House; Jeffries House; Jeffries-Bruce House; John Russell Jones House; Jones Place; Jumping Branch]
  - Albemarle County Houses-K n.d. (Box 57)
    [Keelona (Red Brook); Keith House; Kelly House; John Kelly House; Kenridge; Kenwood; Keswick; Key House; Key West; Kinloch]
  - Albemarle County Houses-L n.d. (Box 57)
    [Lands End; Leake House; Leathers House; Leitch-Haden House; Leitch-Munday House; Lennox Farm; Lewis Level; Lewis Mountain (Kearney House); Lewis-Hanckel House; Licking; Limestone Farm; Linden; Lindsay House; Lipop House; Little Mountain (Locust Grove); Little Virginia; Locust Farm; Locust Grove; Locust Hill; Log House; Logon; Lone Oak Farm; Longly House; Longwood; Lyman Mansion; Lynchburg Road House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ma-Mi n.d. (Box 57)
    [Malvern House; Manahan House; Maple Hill Cottage; Margueritta Crescoli Brothel; Marshall-Rucker House; Martin House; Massie-Wills Townhouse; Matthews House; Maupin House (Creek Dave); Nathaniel Maupin House; Maupin-Bibb House; Maxfield; McAllister-Andrews House; Paul McIntire House; McCue House; Meachum River Farm; Meadow Bluffs (Harris House); Meadow Brook; The Meadows; The Meadows (Lindsay); Merry Oaks; Midmont; Midway; Midway Farm; Millburne; Millington; Milton Farm]
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County Houses-Mor-Mos n.d. (Box 58)
    [Monroe Hill; Montebello; Monticello; Monticola; Moon House, Batesville; Moon-Henderson House; Mooreland; Morea; Isaac Kimber Moran House; Morris House; Morrisena; Morven; Morven-Birckhead]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Mou-Mu n.d. (Box 58)
    [Mount Air; Mount Armour; Mount Comfort; Mount Eagle; Mount Fair; Mount Grove; Mount Ida; Mount Pleasant; Mount Prospect; Mount Walla; Mount Warren; Mountain View (Harkaway); Music Hall]
  - Albemarle County Houses-N n.d. (Box 58)
    [John Neilson House; New Shadwell; New Woodville; Normandale; Joseph Norris House; Norris-McCue House; Norvell House; Nydrie]
  - Albemarle County Houses-O n.d. (Box 58)
    [Oak Crest; Oak Forest, Farmington; Oak Hill; Oak Hill, Greenwood; Oaklands; Oaklawn; The Oaks; Old Hall, Scottsville; James Oldham House; Old Longwood; Old Mooreland]
  - Albemarle County Houses-P n.d. (Box 58)
    [Page Brook; Pantops Water Tower; Parson's Green; Patton House; Paxton Place; Perkins House; Petit House; Peyton House; Piedmont (Wallace), Greenwood; Piedmont, Whitehall; Piedmont, University of Virginia; Piedmont Manor; Pine Knot; Piney Grove, Brookhill; Pines (Terrell); Pireus; Plain Dealing; Plainview Farm; Pleasant Hill (Barksdale); Plumb Pleasant; Powell House; Price-Poore House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Q n.d. (Box 58)
    [Quandry; Quarters]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Ra-Rig n.d. (Box 58)
    [Ragged Mountain Farm; Ramsay-Langhorne-Gibson House; Recoleta; Redlands Club; Red Hill; Refuge; Richlands; Ridgely; Ridgeway; Riggory]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Redlands n.d. (Box 58)
  - Albemarle County Houses-Riv-Ru n.d. (Box 58)
    [Riverdale; Riverdell; Rivanna Farm; River Lawn; River View, Scottsville; Rock Hill; Giles Rogers House; Rogers Place; Rollings Acres; Rosehill; Rosemont; Roundtop; Royal Orchard; Rugby Road Houses; Rutledge]
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County Houses-Se-So n.d. (Box 59)
    [Seven Oaks; Shack Mountain; The Shadows; Shadwell; Shelton House; Sherwood; Shirland; Simpson House; Smith Place; John M. Smith House; Sneed House; Solitude; Southall-Venable House; Southern Comfort; Sowell House]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Sp-Su n.d. (Box 59)
    [Spring Dale; Spring Hill; Stanford Hall; Stevens Place; Stonefield; Stonemont; Strange House; Strawberry Hill; Su Casa (Stevens House); Summer Hill; Sunny Bank; Sunnyside; Sutherland Farm (see Solitude)]
  - Albemarle County Houses-T n.d. (Box 59)
    [Tallwood; Tarry; Temple Hill; Temple Place; The Terrace, Scottsville; Terrel House; T. L. Thuman House; Tiverton; Tompkins House, Scottsville; Tower Creek Farm; Tower House; Trice-Towe House; Tripartite House; Tucked Away; Tudor Grove]
  - Albemarle County Houses-U n.d. (Box 59)
    [14 University Circle; 21 University Circle; Updike House; Upper Plantation]
  - Albemarle County Houses-V n.d. (Box 59)
    [Valley Point; Valentine House; Valmont's; Verdant Lawn; Verulam; Viewmont; Villa Crawford (Ashley House); Villino Lambeth; Vowles Townhouse]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Wa-We n.d. (Box 59)
    [Wakefield; William Walker House; Walnut Grove; Walnut Lawn; Walnut Level; Walters-Page House; Walters-Witkin House; Old Cabin near Warren; Watson House; Watson-Wood House; Wavertree Hall; Wertland; Westbury; West Cairns; West Leigh; West Main Street House; Westover]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Wh-Wo n.d. (Box 59)
    [Wheeler Building; Whilton; White Cross; Whitehall Farm; White Pine; Wilhoit; Williams House; Willoughby; Windie Knowe; Windsor; Windsor Hill; Wingfield House; Woodburne; Woodland]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Wo-Wy n.d. (Box 59)
    [Woodlea; Woodson House; Woodville; Old Woodville; Wyndhurst]
  - Albemarle County Houses-Y n.d. (Box 59)
    [Yancey Mill House; Yeargin House; York House; Dr. Young's House]
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County-Barns and Outbuildings n.d. (Box 60)
    [Carrsville Orchard Barn; Ben Coolyn Double Crib Barn; Log Barn, Brown's Cove; Castalia Barn; Ingleridge; Miller Place Barn, Free Union; Nydrie Stables; Page-Brook Barn; Redlands Barn-Threshing Machine; West Leigh Barn; Sherwood Barn-Threshing Machine; Stockton Creek Barn; Sutherland Barn; Underhill Tobacco Barn; Wilhoit Barns; Miscellaneous barns]
  - Albemarle County-Depots n.d. (Box 60)
    [C & O Depot; Greenwood Tunnel; Keswick Depot; Mount Eagle Depot; Rose Cottage (trainmaster's house); Scottsville Depot; Shadwell Depot; Southern Depot; Union Station/Southern Railroad Depot; Warren Depot; Log House from Crozet Tunnel Workers Houses]
  - Albemarle County-Ecclesiastical n.d. (Box 60)
    [All Saint's Episcopal Church; Batesville Methodist Church; Bethlehem Methodist Church; Beth Shalom Synagogue; Blue Ridge Sanitarium Chapel; Buck Island Church; Buck Mountain Episcopal Church Bell Tower; Centenary Methodist Church South; Charlottesville Christ Church; Charlottesville Methodist Church; Charlottesville Methodist Episcopal Church South; Charlottesville Presbyterian Church; Chestnut Grove Baptist Church; Christ Church Glendower; Christian Church; Christian Science Church; Church West of Boonesville; Church or our Savior; Cove Presbyterian Church; Covesville Church; Earlysville Union Church; Edgehill Chapel; First Baptist Church, Charlottesville; First Methodist Church, Charlottesville; First Presbyterian Church, Park Street; Free Union Baptist Church; Garth Chapel; Grace Church]
    [High Street Baptist Church; Hillsboro Baptist Church; Hodges' Episcopal Manse; Holy Comforter Catholic Church; Mountain Plains Presbyterian Church; Mount Calvary Baptist Church; Mount Ed Baptist Church; Mount Moriah Methodist Church; Mount Sinai Baptist Church; The Rectory; Sand Road Baptist Church; Scottsville Baptist Church; Scottsville Disciples of Christ Church; Scottsville Methodist Church; Scottsville Presbyterian Church; Sharon Church; St. Anne's Parish, Glebe; St. James Episcopal Chapel/Garth Chapel; St. John's Episcopal Church, Scottsville; St. John's Church; St. Luke's Episcopal Church; St. Paul's Episcopal Church; South Plains Presbyterian Church; University Baptist Church; Union Ridge Baptist Church; Unitarian Church; Westminster Presbyterian Church; Woolen Mills Chapel; Zion Baptist Church]
  - Albemarle County-Mills n.d. (Box 60)
    [Cochran's Mill; Cocke's Mill/Johnson's Mill; Crossroad Mill; Dawson's Millhouse; Dwyer's Millhouse; Eolus Mill; Harris Mill; Hartman's Mill; Hatton Grange Mill; Hydraulic, Redbrook; Ivy Mill; Jarman-Harris Millhouse; Peter Jefferson Mill; Kinloch Mill; Lochlyn Millhouse; Maupin House outbuilding; Meadow Run Mill; Merrie Mill; Minor's Mill; Monroe Mill; Scottsville Mill; Smith's Mill; Stockton Creek Mill/Patterson's Mill, Yancey Mills; Stover's Mill; Thacker-Dawson Mill; Tsuquatantia Millhouse; Walker Mill; Walker Millhouse; Warren Mill; Wheat Threshing Machine; Woolen Mills Dam]
  - Albemarle County-Schools n.d. (Box 60)
    [Burnley School; Cismont School; Clark School; Covesville School; Crozet School; Earlysville School; Esmont School; Glendower School; Greenwood School for Boys; Jefferson School; Lane High School; Liberty School; McGuffey School; McIntire School; Midway School; Miller School; Mount Alto School; Piedmont Female Academy; Red Hill School; Rio Road School; Scottsville High School; Old St. Anne's School; Stannes School; Venable School]
  - Albemarle County-Statues n.d. (Box 60)
    [The Dell, University of Virginia; Rotunda Marble Capitol fragment, 1895 fire; Confederate Monument, University of Virginia Cemetery; Civil War Statue; George Rogers Clark Monument; Homer Statue; Jackson Statue; Robert E. Lee Statue; Washington Statue]
  - Albemarle County-Stores n.d. (Box 60)
    [Anderson Brothers Bookstore; Angus Headquarters; Armstrong Knitting Factory; Bishop's Store; Canal Warehouse, Scottsville; Craig's Store; Crossroads Store; H. I. Davis Store; Earlysville Post Office; R. N. Estes' Store; Foster Layman Store; Fry's Spring Gas Station; Hatton Store; Heard's Store; Holsinger Studio & Mr. M. L. Grigg Office; Ivy Stock; Keller & George; Kelly-Bragg Warehouse; Keswick Store; Charles King's Warehouses; Maupin Store; McKee Block; Monticello Dairy; National Bank; Number Nothing; Parrish Store; People's National Bank 2; Powell's Store; Ragged Mountain Service Station; Scottsville Tobacco Warehouse; Warren Store; Wyant Store, White Hall]
  - Albemarle County-Taverns and Hotels n.d. (Box 60)
    [Afton Mountain Top Hotel; Albemarle Hotel; Black's Tavern at Seven Oaks; Boyd's Tavern; Brooksville; Browning-Dettor Tavern; Burnley Tavern; Cabell House; Carlton House-chimney curtain & gable lunette; Castiglione; Clarksville/Sunnyside; Crossroads Tavern; Dolley Madison Inn; DS Tavern; Eagle Tavern; Farish House; Garland A. Garth's Tavern; Garth Tavern; Grasty-Brown Tavern; Green Teapot Inn, Yancey Mills; Hardendale; Jefferson Park Hotel; Jefferson Hotel; La Fourche Tavern; Locust Dale Inn; Locust Grove Tavern; Milton Tavern/Locust Grove; Long's Tavern; Michie Tavern; Monticello Hotel; North of West Main Street; Number Nothing; Price's Hotel; Queen Charlotte Hotel; Scottsville Tavern; Thomas Jefferson Inn; Town & Country Restaurant; Warren Tavern; Warren Stone Tavern; White Hall Inn; Woodstock Hall; Woolen Mills Tavern; Yancey's Tavern]
  - Albemarle County-Miscellaneous Non-House n.d. (Box 60)
    [Albemarle County Courthouse; Albemarle County Jail; Albemarle County Office Building; Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks; Brick Bonds; Buck Mountain Road Trace; Charlottesville Courthouse; Scottsville Road to Charlottesville building; section of Jefferson Memorial Road; Main Street, Charlottesville; Charlottesville Post Office; First Courthouse Column; Court Square; Fray's Mill Bridge; Free Bridge; Howardsville Masonic Lodge; Jefferson Theatre; Levy Opera House; Magruder Sanitarium; Martha Jefferson Hospital; McIntire Library; Miramont Apartments; Nelson Sanitarium; Falls of S. F. Hardware River; Tom Brady & Bill Randolph, Iron Stone at Old's Forge; N. Hardware River; Paramount Theatre; Piedmont Icehouse; Poorhouse Farm; Sunnyside Poorhouse 1; Preston Court Apartments; Race Out Thru Rock, Old's Furnace, S. R. Hardware River; Revolutionary War Barracks; Virginia National Guard Armory; Vinegar Hill Scene; Warren; Village of Esmont; unidentified; portrait of James W. Widderfield; photographs of James W. Widderfield, John Jordan, William Dundum and Dabney Cosby]
    [Alberene; Bank Barn at Enniscorthy; Bank of Crozet; Branchlands; Albemarle County Courthouse; Book of Ebenezer Baptist Church; Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks; Carr Garage; Court Square; Elderly Ladies Home; Farish House; Redland Club; Levy Opera House; Warehouse; W. Main Street; John Yeargin House; Rural life]
- Photographs
  - Albemarle County-Buck Mountain Road-unidentified n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-Three Notch'd Road-unidentified n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-Maps and Plats n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-Unidentified n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-University of Virginia n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-University of Virginia: Birdwood Water Tower n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County-University of Virginia Fraternities n.d. (Box 61)
  - Albemarle County--University of Virginia Pavilions and Hotels n.d. (Box 61)
- Photographs
  - Alexandria n.d. (Box 62)
  - Amherst County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Augusta County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Bath County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Bedford County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Buckingham County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Charles City County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Culpeper n.d. (Box 62)
  - Cumberland County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Fluvanna County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Goochland County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Greene County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Halifax County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Hanover County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Highland County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Lancaster County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Louisa County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Lynchburg n.d. (Box 62)
  - Madison County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Nelson County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Orange County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Pittsylvania County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Richmond n.d. (Box 62)
  - Rockbridge County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Rockingham County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Washington County n.d. (Box 62)
  - Virginia Counties-Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 62)
- Photographs
  - Architecture of Jefferson Country: Dwellings A-Z (31/2 x5) n.d. (Box 63)
  - Architecture of Jefferson Country: Dwellings A-Z (4x6; 5x7) n.d. (Box 63)
  - Architecture of Jefferson Country: Dwellings A-Z (8x10) n.d. (Box 63)
  - Architecture of Jefferson Country: Other Buildings n.d. (Box 63)
  - Architecture of Jefferson Country: Line Art (2 folders) n.d. (Box 63)
  - "Architectural Surveys Associated with Early Road Systems," Association for Preservation Technology Bulletin1980 (Box 63)
  - A Virginia Family and its Plantation Houses 1987 (Box 63)
- Photographs
  - Pennsylvania Folk-life article (4 folders) 1982 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Architecture of the18th-19th Centuries Seminar 1995-1999 (Box 64)
  - District of Columbia n.d. (Box 64)
  - Maryland n.d. (Box 64)
  - North Carolina & South Carolina n.d. (Box 64)
  - West Virginia n.d. (Box 64)
  - Other States n.d. (Box 64)
- Negatives
  - Albemarle Quad 1, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle Quad 2, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle Quad 3, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle Quad 4, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle County Houses, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle County Non-Houses, b & w n.d. (Box 65)
  - Albemarle, positive transparencies of measured drawings n.d. (Box 65)
- Negatives
  - Albemarle County Various Buildings, b & w (3 folders) n.d. (Box 66)
  - Virginia Cities and Counties, 35mm color n.d. (Box 66)
  - Virginia Counties, b & w (2 folders) n.d. (Box 66)
  - Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 66)
  - Eugene Bradbury Drawings n.d. (Box 66)
  - Publication Graphics n.d. (Box 66)
- Negatives
  - Coles Family, contact sheets n.d. (Box 67)
  - Albemarle County, measured drawings, b & w n.d. (Box 67)
  - United States and European Cities, b & w n.d. (Box 67)
- Oversize Drawings and Maps
  - Architectural Drawings, Historical American Buildings Survey
  - Peterson Prize Awards given to Measured Drawings to University of Virginia Architecture Students n.d. (Box Oversize Box S-63)
  - Albemarle County E911 Map Book n.d. (Box Oversize Box S-64)
  - Mounted United States Geological Survey Maps 7.5 MIN (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Barboursville 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Boswell's Tavern 1970 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Boyd Tavern 1970 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Brown's Cove 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Charlottesville East 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Charlottesville West 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Covesville 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Crimora 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Crozet 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Earlysville 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Esmont 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Fletcher Alberene 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Free Union 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Gordonsville 1970 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Howardsville 1968 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Greenfield 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Keswick 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Madison 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - McGaheysville 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - McGaheysville 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Old Rag Mountain 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Rochelle 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Scottsville 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Schuyler 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Simeon 1967 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Stanardsville 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Swift Run Gap 1965 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
    - Waynesboro East 1964 (Box Oversize Box T-18)
- Architectural Drawings, Historical American Buildings Survey
  - University of Virginia Buildings: 1982-1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Anatomical Theatre (7 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Buckingham Palace, Carrs Hill (3 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - The Crackerbox (3 sheets) 1983 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Hotel A (10 sheets) - 2 sets 1988 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Hotel C (8 sheets) 1984 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Hotel E, details 1986 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Hotel E, section 1986 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Hotel E (8 sheets) 1986 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I, east elevation 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I, south elevation 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I (6 sheets) 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I (8 sheets) 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I (7 sheets) - 2 sets 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion I (12 sheets) 1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion II (6 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion III (10 sheets) 1985 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion IV (9 sheets) 1984 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion VIII (9 sheets) - 2 sets 1986 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion IX (6 sheets) 1982 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion IX (11 sheets) - 2 sets 1988 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Pavilion X (8 sheets) 1982 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Albemarle County Buildings: 1976-1989 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Ashlawn (9 sheets) 1980 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Massie-Wills House (5 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Monroe Hill Law Office, Charlottesville (4 sheets) 1981 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Monroe Law Office, Limestone, Keswick (8 sheets) - 2 sets 1977 (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Poplar Forest, Bedford County (6 sheets) - 2 sets n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
  - Miscellaneous floor plans n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-19)
- Architectural Drawings, Historical American Buildings Survey
  - Ecclesiastical: 1977-1986 (Box Oversize Box T-20)
  - Buck Mountain Episcopal Church (6 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-20)
  - Christ Church, Glendower (8 sheets) - 2 sets n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-20)
  - Christ Church, Glendower (7 sheets) n.d. (Box Oversize Box T-20)